Finding Aid for the United States Ephemera Collection LSC.0609
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Polio. SEE: Poliomyelitis. (Box Unknown container 238 for instance of Polio. SEE: Poliomyelitis.)
- Poliomyelitis. (Box 117)
- Pomerene, Atlee, 1863-1937. (Box 55)
- Pond, James Burton, 1838-1903. (Box 55)
- Poore, Benjamin Perley, 1820-1887. (Box 55)
- Pope, John, 1822-1892. (Box 55)
- Porter, Albert Gallatin, 1824-1897. (Box 55)
- Porter, Bernard Harden, 1911 - (Box 55)
- Porter, David Dixon, 1813-1891. (Box 55)
- Porter, David, 1780-1843. (Box 55)
- Porter, Fitz-John, 1822-1901. (Box 55)
- Porter, John Addison, 1856-1900. (Box 55)
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1894 - (Box 55)
- Porter, Noah, 1811-1892. (Box 55)
- Porter, William Sydney, 1862-1910. (Box 55)
- Portland, Maine. (Box 55)
- Portland, Oregon. (Box 55)
- Post, Louis Freeland, 1849-1928. (Box 55)
- Postage-stamps-collectors and collecting. (Box 117)
- Postal service-U.S. (Box 55)
- Potter, Henry Codman, 1835-1908. (Box 55)
- Pound, Ezra Loomis, 1885 - (Box 55)
- Powell, Edward Alexander, 1879 - (Box 109)
- Powell, John Wesley, 1834-1902. (Box 109)
- Powell, Lyman Pierson, 1866-1946. (Box 56)
- Power, Frederick Tyrone, 1869-1931. (Box 56)
- Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873. (Box 56)
- Prang, Louis, 1824-1909. (Box 56)
- Prentice, George Dennison, 1802-1870. (Box 56)
- Prescott, William Hickling, 1796-1859. (Box 56)
- Press-U.S. (Box 56)
- Prime, Samuel Irenaeus, 1812-1885. (Box 56)
- Printed ephemera. (Box 56)
- Progressive Party (U.S.) (Box 56)
- Prohibition., [5 folders.] (Box 91)
- Prokosch, Frederic, 1908 - (Box 56)
- Provo, Utah-description and travel. (Box 56)
- Puerto Rico. (Box 56)
- Puppeteers. (Box 56)
- Putnam, Frederick Ward, 1839-1915. (Box 56)
- Putnam, Herbert, 1861 - (Box 56)
- Pyle, Howard, 1853-1911. (Box 56)
- Quay, Matthew Stanley, 1833-1904. (Box 56)
- Quincy, Josiah, 1772-1864. (Box 56)
- Quitman, John Anthony, 1798-1858. (Box 56)
- Radio industry and trade. (Box 56)
- Railroads-U.S., [2 folders.] (Box 91)
- Railroads-U.S., [5 folders.] (Box 92)
- Rampart College. (Box 56)
- Randolph, John, 1773-1833. (Box 56)
- Ray, Man, 1890 - (Box 56)
- Raymond, Henry Jarvis, 1820-1869. (Box 109)
- Raymond, John Howard, 1814-1878. (Box 109)
- Read, Opie Percival, 1852-1939. (Box 109)
- Read, Thomas Buchanan, 1822-1972. (Box 109)
- Reagan, Ronald (Box 109)
- Reconstruction. (Box 109)
- Redfield, William Cox, 1858-1932. (Box 57)
- Reef Point Gardens. Bar Harbor, Maine. (Box 57)
- Refuse incinerators. (Box 57)
- Reid, Whitelaw, 1837-1912. (Box 57)
- Religious literature., [5 folders.] (Box 93)
- Religious literature., [5 folders.] (Box 126)
- Religious music. (Box 117)
- Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909. (Box 57)
- Repplier, Agnes, 1858-1950. (Box 57)
- Republican Party., [5 folders.] (Box 94)
- Republican Party., [5 folders.] (Box 95)
- Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Box 117)
- Revere, Paul, 1735-1818. (Box 57)
- Rexdale, Robert, 1856 - (Box 57)
- Richmond. (Box 57)
- Ridpath, James. (Box 57)
- Ridpath, John Clark, 1840-1900. (Box 57)
- Riis, Jacob August, 1849-1914. (Box 57)
- Riley, James Whitcomb, 1849-1914. (Box 57)
- Rinehart, Mary (Roberts), 1876-1958. (Box 57)
- Ripley, Edward Payson, 1845-1920. (Box 57)
- Rittenhouse, David, 1732-1796. (Box 57)
- Rives, Hallie Erminie, 1876 - (Box 57)
- Roberts, Elizabeth Madox, 1886-1941. (Box 57)
- Roberts, Kenneth Lewis, 1885 - (Box 57)
- Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976. (Box 57)
- Robins, Raymond, 1873-1954. (Box 57)
- Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1869-1935. (Box 57)
- Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich, 1908-1979. (Box 57)
- Rockledge, Fla. (Box 57)
- Rocky Mountains. (Box 57)
- Rodgers, John Rankin, 1838-1901. (Box 57)
- Rodney, George Brydges, 1719-1792. (Box 57)
- Roe, Edward Payson, 1838-1888. (Box 57)
- Rollins, Edward Henry, 1824-1889. (Box 57)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (Roosevelt), 1884-1962. (Box 57)
- Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 57)
- Root, Elihu, 1845-1937. (Box 57)
- Rosecrans, William Starke, 1819-1989. (Box 110)
- Rosenthal, Toby Edward, 1848 - (Box 110)
- Rush, Benjamin, 1745-1813. (Box 110)
- Rush, Richard, 1780-1859. (Box 110)
- Rusk, Jeremiah McClain, 1830-1893. (Box 110)
- Russell, Annie (Yorke), 1869-1936. (Box 110)
- Russell, Charles Edward, 1860-1941. (Box 58)
- Russell, Charles Marion, 1864-1926. (Box 58)
- Ruxton, George Frederick Augustus, 1820-1848. (Box 58)
- Safford, Truman Henry, 1836-1901. (Box 58)
- Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, 1848-1907. (Box 58)
- Salt Lake City. (Box 119)
- Salt Lake City. (Box 58)
- Salt River Valley, Arizona. (Box 58)
- Saltonstall, Leverett, 1892 - (Box 58)
- Salvation Army. (Box 110)
- Sampson, William Thomas, 1840-1902. (Box 110)
- San Antonio, Texas. (Box 110)
- San Francisco Peaks, Arizona. (Box 110)
- Sandburg, Carl, 1878 - (Box 110)
- Sanger, Margaret (Higgins), 1883 - (Box 110)
- Sangster, Margaret Elizabeth Munson, 1838-1912. (Box 110)
- Santa Fe Trail. (Box 59)
- Santa Fe, New Mexico., [2 folders.] (Box 59)
- Santee, Ross, 1889-1965. (Box 59)
- Sargent, Epes, 1813-1880. (Box 59)
- Savage, Minot Judson, 1841-1918. (Box 59)
- Sayre, Robert Heysham, 1824-1907. (Box 59)
- Schaeffer, Gustave. (Box 59)
- Schaeffer, Nathan Christi, 1849-1919. (Box 59)
- Schaff, Philip, 1819-1893. (Box 59)
- Schenck, Robert Cumming, 1809-1890. (Box 59)
- Schnelling, Felix Emanuel, 1858-1945. (Box 59)
- Schofield, John McAllister, 1831-1906. (Box 59)
- Schrembs, Joseph, Abp., 1866 - (Box 59)
- Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1854-1942. (Box 59)
- Schurz, Carl, 1829-1906. (Box 59)
- Schütze, Eva Watson, 1864-1935. (Box 59)
- Schuyler, Eugene, 1840-1890. (Box 59)
- Schuyler, Karl Cortlandt, 1877-1933. (Box 59)
- Schwab, Charles M., 1862-1939. (Box 59)
- Schwartz, Delmore, 1813-1966. (Box 59)
- Science fiction-bibliography-catalogues. (Box 117)
- Science fiction-Book dealers' catalogs., [5 folders.] (Box 96)
- Scollard, Clinton, 1860-1932. (Box 59)
- Scott, Winfield, 1786-1866. (Box 59)
- Seaman, Elizabeth (Cochrane), 1864-1922. (Box 59)
- Seasongood, Lewis. (Box 59)
- Seattle, Washington. (Box 110)
- Sedgwick, Anne Douglas, 1873-1935. (Box 110)
- Sedgwick, Catherine Maria, 1789-1867. (Box 110)
- Seiberling, Francis A., 1870-1945. (Box 110)
- Serviss, Garrett Putnam, 1851-1929. (Box 110)
- Seton, Ernest Thompson, 1860-1946. (Box 60)
- Seward, William Henry, 1801-1872. (Box 60)
- Sex instruction. (Box 117)
- Seymour, Horatio, 1810-1886. (Box 60)
- Shanklin, George Sea, 1807-1883. (Box 60)
- Shaw, Anna Howard, 1847-1919. (Box 60)
- Shawn, Ted, 1891 - (Box 60)
- Shelby, Isaac, 1750-1826. (Box 60)
- Sheldon, Charles Monroe, 1857-1946. (Box 60)
- Sheppard, Morris, 1875-1941. (Box 60)
- Sheridan, Philip Henry, 1831-1888. (Box 60)
- Sherman, John, 1823-1900. (Box 60)
- Sherman, Lawrence Yates, 1858-1939. (Box 60)
- Sherman, Roger, 1721-1793. (Box 60)
- Sherman, William Tecumseh, 1820-1891. (Box 60)
- Shields, John Knight, 1858-1934. (Box 60)
- Shillaber, Benjamin Penhallow, 1814-1890. (Box 60)
- Shiras, George, 1832-1924. (Box 60)
- Shoes-United States. (Box 60)
- Sickel, Howard Sylvester Jackson, 1880 - (Box 60)
- Sidis, William James, 1898-1944. (Box 60)
- Sierra Club. (Box 60)
- Sigel, Franz, 1824-1902. (Box 60)
- Sigourney, Ludia Howard (Huntley), 1791-1865. (Box 60)
- Silliman, Benjamin, 1816-1885. (Box 60)
- Simmons, Furnifold McLendell, 1854-1940. (Box 60)
- Simms, William Gilmore, 1806-1870. (Box 60)
- Simpson, Jerry, 1842-1905. (Box 60)
- Simpson, Matthew, 1811-1885. (Box 60)
- Siskind, Aaron, 1903-1966. (Box 60)
- Sitgreaves, John, 1740?-1802. (Box 110)
- Skinner, Otis, 1858-1942. (Box 110)
- Slavery in the U.S.-Anti-slavery movements. (Box 110)
- Slicer, Henry, 1801-1874. (Box 110)
- Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944. (Box 110)
- Smith, Edgar Fahs, 1854-1928. (Box 110)
- Smith, Ellison DuRant, 1864-1944. (Box 110)
- Smith, Francis Ormond Jonathan, 1806-1876. (Box 110)
- Smith, Frederick A. (Box 110)
- Smith, Gerrit, 1797-1874. (Box 110)
- Smith, Hoke, 1855-1931. (Box 110)
- Smith, Samuel A., Abp. (Box 110)
- Smithsonian Institution. (Box 61)
- Smoot, Reed, 1862-1941. (Box 61)
- Smyth, Albert Henry, 1863-1907. (Box 61)
- Social history. (Box 61)
- Society of American Archivists. (Box 61)
- Sorin, Edward Frederick, S.J., 1814-1893. (Box 61)
- Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932. (Box 61)
- South Dakota. (Box 110)
- Southwest, New., [2 folders.] (Box 61)
- Southworth, Emma Dorothy Eliza Nevitte, 1819-1899. (Box 111)
- Spahr, Charles Barzillai, 1860-1904. (Box 111)
- Spaulding, Alber, 1888-1953. (Box 111)
- Special Libraries Association. (Box 111)
- Spingarn, Arthur B., 1878-1971. (Box 62)
- Spofford, Ainsworth Rand, 1825-1908. (Box 62)
- Spofford, Harriet Elizabeth Prescott, 1835-1921. (Box 62)
- Spooner, John Coit, 1843-1919. (Box 62)
- Sports. (Box 61)
- Sports. (Box 62)
- Sprague, Frank Julian, 1857-1934. (Box 62)
- Sprague, Kate (Chase), 1840-1899. (Box 62)
- Sprague, William, 1830-1915. (Box 62)
- Springer, Rebecca Ruter, 1832 - (Box 62)
- Squier, Ephraim George, 1821-1888. (Box 62)
- St. Augustine, Fla. (Box 58)
- St. Clair, Arthur, 1734-1818. (Box 58)
- St. Lawrence River. (Box 58)
- St. Louis. (Box 58)
- St. Paul, Minn. (Box 58)
- Standard Oil Company. (Box 62)
- Stanlaws, Penrhyn. (Box 62)
- Stanley, J.B. (Box 62)
- Stanton, Edwin McMasters, 1814-1869. (Box 62)
- Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1815-1902. (Box 62)
- Starr, Frederick, 1858-1933. (Box 62)
- Steadman, Ralph. (Box 62)
- Stearns, Frederic Pike, 1851-1919. (Box 62)
- Steel-U.S. (Box 62)
- Steffens, Joseph Lincoln, 1866-1936. (Box 62)
- Steichen, Edward, 1897 - (Box 62)
- Stein, Gertrude, 1874-1946., [2 folders.] (Box 62)
- Steloff, Frances, 1887 - (Box 62)
- Stephens, Alexander Hamilton, 1812-1883. (Box 62)
- Sternberg, George Miller, 1838-1915. (Box 62)
- Stetina, Fran, 1837 - (Box 62)
- Stetson, John Batterson, 1830-1906. (Box 111)
- Stevens, Lillian M.N., 1844-1914. (Box 111)
- Stevens, Wallace, 1879-1955. (Box 111)
- Stevenson, Adlai Ewing, 1900-1965. (Box 111)
- Stevenson, Sarah Yorke, 1847-1921. (Box 111)
- Stewart, William Morris, 1827-1909. (Box 111)
- Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946. (Box 63)
- Stillé, Charles Janeway, 1819-1899. (Box 63)
- Stockton, Frank Richard, 1834-1902. (Box 63)
- Stoddard, Richard Henry, 1825-1903. (Box 63)
- Stone, Lucy, 1818-1893. (Box 63)
- Stone, William Joel, 1848-1918. (Box 63)
- Storrs, Richard Salter, 1821-1900. (Box 63)
- Story, Joseph, 1779-1845. (Box 63)
- Stoughton, Edwin Wallace, 1818-1822. (Box 63)
- Stowe, Harriet Elizabeth (Beecher), 1811-1896. (Box 63)
- Strain family. (Box 63)
- Strakosch, Clara Louise (Kellogg), 1842-1916. (Box 63)
- Straus, Nathan, 1848-1931. (Box 63)
- Straus, Oscar Solomon, 1850-1926. (Box 63)
- Stringham, Silas Horton, 1797-1876. (Box 63)
- Strong, Josiah, 1847-1916. (Box 63)
- Stuart, James Ewell Brown, 1833-1864. (Box 63)
- Summerhayes, Martha, 1846-1911. (Box 63)
- Sumner, Charles, 1811-1874. (Box 63)
- Sumner, William Graham, 1840-1910. (Box 63)
- Sun (The). New York. (Box 63)
- Sunset Crater National Monument. (Box 63)
- Swann, John. (Box 63)
- Swanson, Claude Augustus, 1862-1949. (Box 63)
- Swift, George B. (Box 63)
- Swing, David, 1830-1894. (Box 63)
- Sykes, Godfrey Glenton, 1861-1948. (Box 63)
- Tacoma, Washington. (Box 63)
- Taft, Alphonzo, 1810-1891. (Box 63)
- Taliesen West (Scottsdale, AZ) (Box 63)
- Tallmadge, Benjamin, 1754-1835. (Box 63)
- Taney, Roger Brooke, 1777-1864. (Box 63)
- Tarbell, Ida Minerva, 1857-1943. (Box 63)
- Tarkington, Booth, 1869-1946. (Box 63)
- Taxation. (Box 111)
- Taylor, Peter Hillsman, 1917 - (Box 111)
- Teasdale, Sara, 1884-1933. (Box 111)
- Technocracy, Inc. (Box 111)
- Telephones-history. (Box 111)
- Television. (Box 111)
- Teller, Henry Moore, 1830-1914. (Box 64)
- Temperance societies. (Box 64)
- Tennent, Gilbert, 1703-1764. (Box 64)
- Tennessee Valley Authority. (Box 64)
- Tennessee. (Box 64)
- Terhune, Mrs. Mary Virginia (Hawes), 1831-1922. (Box 64)
- Terry, William H. (Box 64)
- Tesla, Nikola, 1856-1943. (Box 64)
- Texas-annexation to the U.S. (Box 64)
- Texas., [2 folders.] (Box 64)
- Thanksgiving Day proclamations. (Box 64)
- Thanksgiving Day proclamations. (Box 122)
- Thaxter, Celia (Laighton), 1835-1894. (Box 64)
- Thayer, George Augustine, 18379-1925. (Box 64)
- Thayer, Tiffany, 1902 - (Box 64)
- Theaters. (Box 111)
- Thomas, Charles Spaudling, 1849-1934. (Box 111)
- Thomas, Edith Matilda, 1854-1925. (Box 111)
- Thomas, George Henry, 1816-1870. (Box 111)
- Thomas, Theodore, 1835-1905. (Box 111)
- Thompson, Maurice, 1844-1901. (Box 111)
- Thoreau, Henry David, 1817-1862. (Box 111)
- Thornwell, James Henley, 1812-1862. (Box 111)
- Thorpe, Mrs. Rose (Hartwick), 1850-1939. (Box 111)
- Thurber, James, 1894 - (Box 111)
- Thurman, Allen Granberry, 1813-1895. (Box 65)
- Thurston, John Mellen, 1847-1916. (Box 65)
- Tillman, Benjamin Ryan, 1847-1918. (Box 65)
- Time. (Box Unknown container 239 for instance of Time.)
- Tobacco industry-U.S. (Box 65)
- Toklas, Alice Babette. (Box 65)
- Tombstone, Arizona. (Box 65)
- Tourgee, Albion Winegar, 1838-1899. (Box 65)
- Towne, Charles Arnette, 1858-1928. (Box 65)
- Townsend Plan, Inc. (Box 65)
- Toys. (Box 65)
- Trade-unions. (Box 65)
- Train, George Francis, 1829-1904. (Box 65)
- Tramps. (Box 65)
- Transportation. (Box 112)
- Travel. (Box 117)
- Trine, Ralph Waldo, 1866 - (Box 66)
- Trinidad, Colorado. (Box 66)
- Tripler, Charles E. (Box 66)
- Trowbridge, John Townsend, 1827-1916. (Box 66)
- Trumbull, Lyman, 1813-1896. (Box 66)
- Tucson, Arizona. (Box 66)
- Tudor, Tasha, 1915 - (Box 66)
- Tumulty, Joseph Patrick, 1879 - (Box 66)
- U.S.-boundaries-Canada. (Box 67)
- U.S.-description and travel. (Box 67)
- U.S.-Description and travel., [5 folders.] (Box 100)
- U.S.-emigration and immigration. (Box 67)
- U.S.-foreign relations-Mexico. (Box 67)
- U.S.-forestry. (Box 67)
- U.S. General Land Office. (Box 67)
- U.S.-government-Social Security. (Box 67)
- U.S.-government. (Box 67)
- U.S.-history-centennial celebrations, etc. (Box 117)
- U.S.-history-Civil War., [5 folders.] (Box 97)
- U.S.-history-Northwest. (Box 112)
- U.S.-history-Revolution. (Box 112)
- U.S.-history-War of 1898. (Box 112)
- U.S.-history. (Box 67)
- U.S. National Archives. Facsimile series. (Box Unknown container 240 for instance of U.S. National Archives. Facsimile series.)
- U.S.-politics and government-1783-1865. (Box 98)
- U.S.-politics and government-1900-1964., [2 folders.] (Box 98)
- U.S.-politics and government-1965-1970. (Box 98)
- U.S.-politics and government-1971. (Box 98)
- U.S.-politics and government-1972-1973. (Box 98)
- U.S.-politics and government-1974. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1975. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1976. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1977. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1978. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1979. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1980. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1981. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1982. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1983. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1984. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-1992. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-miscellaneous. (Box 99)
- U.S.-politics and government-Social Security. (Box 67)
- U.S.-public lands. (Box 67)
- U.S.-societies. (Box 68)
- U.S. Treasury Department. (Box 68)
- U.S. Army-history-Civil War. (Box 67)
- U.S. Army. (Box 67)
- U.S. Bureau of Standards. International Metric System. (Box Unknown container 241 for instance of U.S. Bureau of Standards. International Metric System.)
- U.S. Census-1960. (Box 67)
- U.S. Census-1970. (Box 67)
- U.S. Congress, House, Committee on Unamerican Activites. (Box 67)
- U.S. Naval Academy, Annapolis. (Box 68)
- U.S. Navy. (Box 68)
- Uncensored. New York., [2 folders.] (Box 66)
- Underwood, Oscar Wilder, 1862-1929. (Box 66)
- United Nations-San Francisco. (Box 67)
- Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-1940. (Box 68)
- Untermeyer, Samuel, 1858-1940. (Box 68)
- Updike, Daniel Berkeley, 1860-1941. (Box 68)
- Utah State Historical Society, Salt Lake City. Newsletter. (Box 68)
- Utah., [2 folders.] (Box 68, Box 131)
- Vail, George I. (Box 68)
- Van DerZee, James, 1887 - (Box 68)
- Van DerZee, James, 1887 - (Box 118)
- Van Dyke, Henry, 1852-1933. (Box 69)
- Van Dyke, John Charles, 1856-1932. (Box 69)
- Van Loon, Hendrick Willem, 1882-1949. (Box 69)
- Van Vechten, Carl, 1880 - (Box 69)
- Vanderbilt, Cornelius, 1794-1877. (Box 68)
- Vanderbilt, Gloria (Morgan), d. 1965. (Box 68)
- Vardaman, James Kimble, 1861-1930. (Box 69)
- Venable, William Henry, 1836-1920. (Box 69)
- Vermont. (Box 69)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars. (Box 69)
- Vicksburg National Military Park. (Box 69)
- Viertel, Peter, 1920 - (Box 69)
- Vilas, William Freeman, 1840-1908. (Box 69)
- Virginia City, Nevada. (Box 69)
- Virginia., [2 folders.] (Box 69)
- Volunteers in Service to America. (Box 69)
- Waco, Texas. (Box Unknown container 242 for instance of Waco, Texas.)
- Wade, Benjamin Franklin, 1800-1878. (Box 69)
- Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, bp., 1792-1854. (Box 69)
- Walcott, Charles Doolittle, 1850-1926. (Box 113)
- Walk, David. (Box 113)
- Walker, James John, 1881-1946. (Box Unknown container 243 for instance of Walker, James John, 1881-1946.)
- Walla Walla, Washington. (Box 113)
- Wallace, Henry Agard, 1888 - (Box 113)
- Wallace, Lewis, 1827-1905. (Box 113)
- Walsh, Thomas F., 1851-1910. (Box 113)
- Walsh, Thomas James, 1859-1933. (Box 113)
- Walter, J.H. (Box 113)
- Warburg, Paul Moritz, 1868 - (Box 113)
- Ward, Charles Henshaw, 1872-1935. (Box 113)
- Ward, Elizabeth Stuart (Phelps), 1844-1911. (Box 113)
- Ward, Henry Augustus, 1834-1906. (Box 113)
- Warhol, Andy. (Box 113)
- Warman, Cy, 1855-1914. (Box 113)
- Warner, Charles Dudley, 1829-1900. (Box 113)
- Warren, Henry White, 1831-1912. (Box 113)
- Warren, Joseph, 1741-1775. (Box 113)
- Warren, Ohio. (Box 113)
- Washburne, Elihu Benjamin, 1816-1887. (Box 70)
- Washington, Booker Talisafero, 1856-1915. (Box 70)
- Washington, D.C., [2 folders.] (Box 70)
- Washington, Mrs. Martha (Dandridge) Custis, 1731- 1801. (Box 70)
- Washington. (Box 70)
- Waters, Frank, 1902 - (Box 113)
- Watson, Thomas Edward, 1856-1922. (Box 113)
- Wayne, Anthony, 1745-1796. (Box 113)
- Weaver, Pauline, 1800-1867. (Box 71)
- Weaver, William. (Box 71)
- Webster, Daniel, 1782-1852. (Box 71)
- Weddings-California. (Box 71)
- Weeks, John Wingate, 1860-1926. (Box 71)
- Welch, William Henry, 1850-1934. (Box 71)
- Welles, Gideon, 1802-1878. (Box 71)
- Wells, Daniel. (Box 71)
- Wells, Fargo and Company. (Box 71)
- Wells, Heber Manning, 1859-1938. (Box 71)
- West (The)-history. (Box 71)
- Western Interstate Library Coordinating Organization. (Box 71)
- Westerners (The). (Box 71)
- Westinghouse, George, 1846-1914. (Box 71)
- Wharton, Edith Newbold (Jones), 1862-1937. (Box 71)
- Wheeler, Burton Kendall, 1882 - (Box 71)
- Whitaker, Ozi William, 1830-1911. (Box 71)
- White House (The), Washington D.C. (Box Unknown container 244 for instance of White House (The), Washington D.C.)
- White Sands, New Mexico. (Box 71)
- White, Andrew Dickson, 1832-1918. (Box 71)
- White, E.B. (Elwyn Brooks), 1899-1985. (Box 71)
- White, Edward Douglass, 1845-1921. (Box 71)
- White, Grace (Miller) (Box 71)
- White, William Allen, 1868-1944. (Box 71)
- White, William, bp., 1748-1836. (Box 71)
- Whiting, George W. (Box 71)
- Whitlock, Brand, 1869-1934. (Box 71)
- Whitman, John Lorin, 1862-1926. (Box 71)
- Whitman, Walt, 1819-1892., [2 folders.] (Box 71)
- Whitney, William Collins, 1841-1904. (Box 113)
- Whitney, William Dwight, 1827-1894. (Box 113)
- Whittier, John Greenleaf, 1807-1892. (Box 113)
- Wickersham, George Woodward, 1858-1936. (Box 72)
- Wickersham, James, 1857-1939. (Box 72)
- Wilberforce, William, 1759-1833. (Box 72)
- Wilcox, Ella Wheeler, 1850-1919. (Box 72)
- Wilder, Thornton Niven, 1897-1975. (Box 72)
- Wildlife conservation. (Box 72)
- Wiley, Harvey Washington, 1844-1930. (Box 72)
- Willard, Frances Elizabeth Caroline, 1839-1898. (Box 72)
- Willcox, Orlando Bolivar, 1823-1907. (Box 72)
- Williams, George Fred, 1852 - (Box 72)
- Williams, John Sharp, 1854-1932. (Box 72)
- Williams, Jonathan. (Box 72)
- Williams, Tennessee, 1911-1983. (Box 72)
- Williams, William Carlos, 1883-1963. (Box 113)
- Williamsburg, Virginia., [2 folders.] (Box 73)
- Williamson, Hugh, 1735-1819. (Box 73)
- Willis, Nathaniel Parker, 1806-1867. (Box 73)
- Willkie, Wendell Lewis, 1892-1944., [2 folders.] (Box 73)
- Wilson, Henry, 1812-1875. (Box 73)
- Wilson, James, 1836-1920. (Box 73)
- Wilson, John Moulder, 1837-1919. (Box 73)
- Wilson, William Bauchop, 1862-1934. (Box 73)
- Windom, William, 1827-1891. (Box 73)
- Winogrand, Garry, 1928 - (Box 73)
- Winthrop, Robert Charles, 1809-1894. (Box 73)
- Wirt, William, 1772-1834. (Box 73)
- Wise, Stephen Samuel, 1872 - (Box 73)
- Wister, Owen, 1860-1938. (Box 73)
- Wit and humor. (Box 114)
- Wolfe, Thomas, 1900-1938., [4 folders.] (Box 123)
- Women-suffrage-U.S. (Box 117)
- Wonton, Jon. (Box 117)
- Wood, Leonard, 1860-1927. (Box 114)
- Woodbury, Levi, 1789-1851. (Box 74)
- Woodruff, Theodore Tuttle, 1811-1892. (Box 74)
- Woodward, Robert Simpson, 1849-1924. (Box 74)
- Worden, John Lorimer, 1818-1897. (Box 74)
- World Monuments Fund, New York. (Box 74)
- Wortham, Henry Mason. (Box 74)
- Wright, Carroll Davidson, 1840-1909. (Box 74)
- Wright, Richard, 1908-1960. (Box 74)
- Wright, Silas, 1795-1847. (Box 74)
- Writers' War Board. (Box 74)
- Wyman, Jeffries, 1714-1874. (Box 74)
- Wyman, Walter, 1848-1911. (Box 74)
- Wyoming. (Box 74)
- Yates, Richard, 1818-1873. (Box 74)
- Yellowstone National Park., [2 folders.] (Box 74)
- Youmans, Edward Livingston, 1821-1887. (Box 74)
- Young America. (Box 114)
- Young, Brigham, 1801-1877. (Box 114)
- Young, Charles Augustus, 1834-1908. (Box 114)
- Young, Ella Flagg, 1845-1918 (Box 114)
- Young, James Thomas, 1873 - (Box 114)
- Young, Thomas L., 1832-1888. (Box 114)
- Yuma, Arizona. (Box 114)
- Zen Buddhism-U.S. (Box 117)
- Zerrahn, Carl, 1826-1909. (Box 114)
- Zimbalist, Efrem, 1889 - (Box 114)
- Zion National Park, Utah. (Box 114)
- Zogbaum, Rufus Fairchild, 1849-1925. (Box 114)
- Zueblin, Charles, 1866-1924. (Box 114)